Being a police officer, you have to carry yourself with dignity and pride.
作为一名警官, 你的举止必须体现尊严和自豪感.
I like being with people. I like helping people.
我喜欢与人打交道. 我喜欢帮助别人.
I still see the child today that I delivered some 10 years ago and, er, it was like a bond.
我仍然经常见到10年前我接生的那个小孩, er, 我们之间仿佛有一条纽带.
We have a very close relationship because the mother spoke to the child and said,
我们关系非常密切, 因为孩子的母亲对孩子说:
"That's the officer that delivered you years ago."
"这就是多年前接生你的那个警官."
That was my most rewarding experience.
那是我收获最大的一次经历.
Let me tell you, statistically, most of the people react favorably toward the police.
让我们看看统计数字吧, 大多数人对警察反应良好.
But again, statistically, the firemen are more loved than the police.
但是统计数字也表明, 消防队员比警察更受喜爱.
At one point, when I, we went in, um, the fire started rolling up over the top of us,
当时, 当我, 当我们进去的时候, um, 火苗在我们头上翻卷着,
so um, they called, they backed everybody out and they hit it with deck guns,
所以, um, 他们招呼着, 他们护送大家都撤出来, 然后再用灭火枪灭火,
and after a while, we were ordered back in, and we went back in and I was going up the stairs,
过了一会儿, 我们奉命进去, 于是我们就又进去了, 我往楼上走,
and on the way up the stairs I looked up, and, er,
在上楼的路上, 我向上看, and, er,
it looks like, you know, it looked like, I thought I could see little, er, little holes of light coming through the ceiling,
好像, you know, 好像, 我想我能看见屋顶有小洞漏进光来,
you know, figuring that, you know, it was burning through.
you know, 我想, you know, 那是烧穿了.
And then I took a closer look and it actually was completely burned off and they were stars up in the sky.
然后我仔细看了看, 事实上屋顶全烧穿了, 那些光是天上的星星.
So the whole roof was gone and that was one of the, er, more wild situations that, that I've been in.
整个屋顶都烧没了. 那是我经历过的比较惊险的一个状况.
And I was just a couple of weeks, er, on the job.
而那时, 我才刚干了几个星期.